<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hindi movies &#8211; CMS Ipolitics</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cms.ipolitics.ca/tag/hindi-movies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cms.ipolitics.ca</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:48:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How did Shahrukh&#8217;s &#8216;Danki&#8217;, &#8216;Danka&#8217; play?</title>
		<link>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/how-did-shahrukhs-danki-danka-play/</link>
					<comments>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/how-did-shahrukhs-danki-danka-play/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[zokjala]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hindi movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shah Rukh Khan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cms.ipolitics.ca/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shahrukh Khan&#8217;s much awaited movie &#8216;Danki&#8217; released early on Thursday morning. From yesterday afternoon on Wednesday, Saj Saj Rob has fallen in different theaters of India. Shah Rukh-lovers were all set to welcome &#8216;Dunky&#8217;. Fans were in a festive mood by beating drums, bursting firecrackers, garlanding cutouts of their favorite superstars. They had reserved tickets [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shahrukh Khan&#8217;s much awaited movie &#8216;Danki&#8217; released early on Thursday morning. From yesterday afternoon on Wednesday, Saj Saj Rob has fallen in different theaters of India. Shah Rukh-lovers were all set to welcome &#8216;Dunky&#8217;. Fans were in a festive mood by beating drums, bursting firecrackers, garlanding cutouts of their favorite superstars. They had reserved tickets in advance to see &#8216;first day first show&#8217;.<br>Movie lovers flocked to watch &#8216;Danki&#8217; early in the morning after leaving office and college. Various reactions of movie lovers have come on social media around this film. According to some, Rajkumar Hirani&#8217;s &#8216;Danki&#8217; is a classic, while others have termed the film as rubbish. The comedy-drama film received mixed reactions on social media. Now let&#8217;s see how well &#8216;Dunky&#8217; can play &#8216;Dunka&#8217;.</p>



<p>Rajkumar Hirani&#8217;s films alone are full of entertainment. But many people said in various reviews on social media, the magic of Rajkumar is missing somewhere in this film. The story of &#8216;Danki&#8217; has touched many people. One person wrote about this film on social media, &#8216;The whole world is affected by &#8220;Dunky&#8221;-mania.&#8217;</p>



<p>Another praised the film and wrote, &#8216;Dunky&#8217; is a great and emotional film. This film will entertain and impress. “Dunky” will take you on an emotional roller coaster ride. Shah Rukh Khan made the audience laugh and entertained. Taapsee Pannu is awesome. Vikram Kochhar, Anil Grover are great.&#8217;<br>Some say the film is full of patriotism. A viewer posted a video saying, “&#8217;Dunky&#8217; is an emotional roller coaster. You will cry and laugh at the same time. People will not forget Vicky Kaushal. And of course he is King Khan (Shahrukh Khan)!&#8217; Another viewer praised the film and wrote, &#8216;Rajkumar proved himself again. The screenplay of the film is excellent. The acting is excellent. This film will forever shine in the world of Hindi cinema. In terms of direction, I don&#8217;t think anyone could have done it better than Rajkumar Hirani.&#8217; There are so many beautiful comments about the movie &#8216;Danki&#8217; flying in the net-world. Everyone is giving love to this film.</p>



<p>Frankly, &#8216;Dunky&#8217; is more Rajkumar Hirani&#8217;s film than Shah Rukh&#8217;s. Everyone has high expectations from a director like him. All the films of Raju Hirani have been fulfilling people&#8217;s expectations for so long. But this time his picture has disappointed many.</p>



<p>One wrote on Facebook, &#8216;The first half of the film is boring. It&#8217;s never SRK&#8217;s film, it&#8217;s Raju Hirani&#8217;s film. SRK never became the lead of the film himself. Every character is important in his films. Photo Jokes Baker. But the emotional scenes will touch the heart. The film will inspire you to go to other countries.&#8217; Another viewer did not like this picture at all. That&#8217;s why he called this film of King Khan a &#8216;disaster&#8217;.</p>



<p>According to another user, this film is the biggest disaster of Rajkumar Hirani&#8217;s career. A viewer commented on Net-Dunya, &#8216;The story is very weak. Some things are a no-brainer. “Dunky” fails to impress us. There is no nominal entertainment. Rajkumar Hirani failed.&#8217; Meanwhile, another commented about &#8216;Dunky&#8217; and wrote, &#8216;This film is for those Indian uncles and aunties who live abroad and want to return to their own land. The youth community will not be able to relate to this film.&#8217;<br>Rajkumar Hirani&#8217;s &#8216;Danki&#8217; stars Shah Rukh Khan as &#8216;Hardy&#8217; and Taapsee Pannu as &#8216;Manu&#8217;. Vicky Kaushal plays an important role in this film. His performance in the film is being appreciated.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/how-did-shahrukhs-danki-danka-play/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
