<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hollywood &#8211; CMS Ipolitics</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cms.ipolitics.ca/tag/hollywood/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cms.ipolitics.ca</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:53:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Actor Jonathan Majors convicted of assault, dropped from Marvel films</title>
		<link>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/actor-jonathan-majors-convicted-of-assault-dropped-from-marvel-films/</link>
					<comments>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/actor-jonathan-majors-convicted-of-assault-dropped-from-marvel-films/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[zokjala]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Actor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Convict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marvel Cinematic Universe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cms.ipolitics.ca/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Actor Jonathan&#160;Majors, a rising Hollywood star who had been set to play the leading role in an upcoming Marvel superhero film, was found guilty by a New York jury on Monday on charges of attacking his ex-girlfriend in the back of a car. Shortly after the verdict, a spokesperson for Walt Disney- owned Marvel said [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Actor Jonathan&nbsp;Majors, a rising Hollywood star who had been set to play the leading role in an upcoming Marvel superhero film, was found guilty by a New York jury on Monday on charges of attacking his ex-girlfriend in the back of a car.</p>



<p>Shortly after the verdict, a spokesperson for Walt Disney- owned Marvel said the studio had dropped the actor from future projects.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Majors portrayed a villain known as Kang the Conqueror in this year&#8217;s ‘Ant-Man’ movie and was scheduled to play the lead role in 2026 release ‘Avengers: The Kang Dynasty’.</p>



<p>Majors&nbsp;had been charged with two counts of assault and two counts of harassment, all misdemeanors. The jury of six convicted him on one count of assault and one count of harassment, and acquitted him of the other charges.</p>



<p>The verdict followed a two-week trial in state court in Manhattan.</p>



<p>Majors, dressed in a gray suit, stood and faced the jury as the foreperson read the verdict. He pursed his lips and cast his face down when the first conviction was read but otherwise showed little reaction.</p>



<p>Majors is set to be sentenced on 6 February. He faces up to a year in prison, but prosecutors have not indicated what sentence they plan to seek. His lawyer did not immediately respond to a request for comment.</p>



<p>The Manhattan District Attorney&#8217;s Office hailed the verdict in a statement, saying the evidence showed a &#8220;cycle of psychological and emotional abuse, and escalating patterns of coercion&#8221; by&nbsp;Majors.</p>



<p>Prosecutors said&nbsp;Majors&nbsp;assaulted his then-girlfriend&nbsp;Grace Jabbari in a hired car in Manhattan in March, leaving her with a broken finger and swollen arm and ear.</p>



<p>Jabbari said over four days of testimony that&nbsp;Majors&nbsp;attacked her after she grabbed his phone upon seeing a text from another woman. She also described his &#8220;violent temper&#8221; and other incidents where he &#8220;exploded&#8221; in anger.</p>



<p>&#8220;She had shaped herself around the defendant, to cater to his personality, to avoid him being angry with her,&#8221;&nbsp;prosecutor Kelli Galaway said during closing arguments on Thursday.</p>



<p>Majors&#8217; lawyer sought to flip the script, claiming it was Jabbari who victimised&nbsp;Majors&nbsp;by attacking him in the car and then falsely accusing him of assault after he broke up with her.</p>



<p>&#8220;You are here to end this nightmare for Jonathan&nbsp;Majors,” lawyer Priya Chaudhry said through tears during her closing argument.</p>



<p>Majors&nbsp;filed his own complaint against Jabbari, prompting her arrest on assault charges in October. But the Manhattan District Attorney&#8217;s Office later closed the case because it &#8220;lacks prosecutorial merit.&#8221;</p>



<p>Majors, 34, starred in the 2019 film ‘The Last Black Man in San Francisco’ before landing top billing in ‘Creed III’ and appearing in ‘Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania’. Majors&nbsp;was dropped by his management company, public relations firm and several advertisers after his arrest.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/actor-jonathan-majors-convicted-of-assault-dropped-from-marvel-films/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 10 list of 100 best TV series of all time</title>
		<link>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/top-10-list-of-100-best-tv-series-of-all-time/</link>
					<comments>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/top-10-list-of-100-best-tv-series-of-all-time/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[zokjala]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the star]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cms.ipolitics.ca/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[American magazine Variety has published the list of the 100 best TV series of all time. This report is about the top 10 series of this list published last Wednesday. 1. i love lucy Topping the list is the famous sitcom series I Love Lucy aired on CBS Television in the United States. Lucille Ball played [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>American magazine Variety has published the list of the 100 best TV series of all time. This report is about the top 10 series of this list published last Wednesday.</p>



<p><strong>1. i love lucy</strong></p>



<p>Topping the list is the famous sitcom series I Love Lucy aired on CBS Television in the United States. Lucille Ball played the title role in the series about the stardom of Lucy Ricardo, a young New York housewife. It also features actress Lucille&#8217;s husband, Desi Arnaz. The series ran for 6 seasons and 180 episodes from October 15, 1951 to May 6, 1957. The series is directed by Mark Daniels, William Asher and James Kern.</p>



<p><strong>2. Mad Men</strong></p>



<p>Second on the list is Mad Men. The story of the series revolves around a famous American advertising company and its boss Donald Draper in the sixties. American actor John Hamm is known for playing this role. The series was created by Matthew Winer. The series aired for seven seasons from 2007 to 2015 on American TV channel AMC.</p>



<p><strong>3. The Sopranos</strong></p>



<p>The crime and psychological genre series is based on the story of a mobster named Tony Soprano. It stars James Gandolfini in the lead role. The series, created by David Chase, aired on HBO from 1999 to 2007.</p>



<p><strong>4. The Simpsons</strong></p>



<p>The animated sitcom series The Simpsons was created by Matt Groening. The culture and lifestyle of the country has come up in the series made about the members of the Simpson family. The series has been airing on Fox television since 1989.</p>



<p><strong>5. breaking bad</strong></p>



<p>American crime drama series Breaking Bad is in the fifth position of the list. The series, created by Vince Gilligan, aired on AMC Networks from 2008 to 2013. It stars Bryan Cranston, Anna Gunn and many others.</p>



<p><strong>6. Sex and the City</strong></p>



<p>The series was created by Darren Starr about four women in New York. It stars Carrie Bradshaw, Charlotte York, Miranda Hobbs and Samantha Jones as the four main characters. The series aired on HBO from 1998 to 2004.</p>



<p><strong>7. The Wire</strong></p>



<p>The crime drama series is produced by David Simon. The series aired on HBO from 2002 to 2008. It stars Dominic West, Lance Radick, John Doman and many others in various roles.</p>



<p><strong>8. Seinfeld</strong></p>



<p>The sitcom series was created by two producers, Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld. The series aired on NBC from 1989 to 1998. It starred Jerry Seinfeld, Jason Alexander and many others.</p>



<p><strong>9. The Mary Taylor Moore Show</strong></p>



<p>The sitcom series aired on CBS from 1970 to 1977. It was created by James L. Brooks and Alan Barnes.</p>



<p><strong>10. Roots</strong></p>



<p>Based on Alex Hale&#8217;s novel Roots: The Saga of an American Family, the TV series was produced by Marvin Chomsky, John Ehrman, David Greene, Gilbert Moses. Lever Burton, Robert Reed and many others acted in this mini series aired on ABC channel in 1977.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cms.ipolitics.ca/top-10-list-of-100-best-tv-series-of-all-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
